# **Edwin Kevin Simental Frayre**

Web Developer

### CONTACT -



+52 618 290 14 05



Kevin55esder@gmail.com



Durango, Dgo.

# **EDUCATION** -

**Materials Science Engineering** UJED - August 2016 - December 2021

Support and maintenance technician of computer equipment

**CBTIS #89** - August 2013 - January 2016.

## **ABILITYS**

- SCRUM
- Kanban
- Programmation logic
- Teamwork
- Autodidact
- Focused on results
- I work under pressure

### LENGUAGES

- Spanish --- Native
- English ---- B2

#### Links

Webpage: Link

Linkedin: Link

### **About Me**

I am a graduate of the Materials Science Engineering career at the Juarez University of the State of Durango. I have approximately working on projects with React, React Native and Node JS. I want to continue specializing in these last technologies and thus continue to acquire more experience, always open to learn. I like to work as a team, I like the analysis and problem solving beyond just programming.

#### SKILLS

- HTML HTML 5
- CSS CSS 3 Sass Bootstrap
- JavaScript jQuery
- SQL PostgreSQL MySQL
- **Python**
- Git GitHub
- React
- Node.js Express
- **MongoDB**

### **EXPERIENCE** -

#### **Customer service**

Atel – September 2022 - march 2023

Analysis of a microparticle for use in the Medicine

UJED - december 2020 - October 2021.

#### COURSES

- JavaScript algorithms and data structures
- The complete web developer in 2022: ZTM
- introducción al desarrollo web